mailvu.com 2012-10-03

# mailVU - mail you can view

## Privacy Policy

**Updated as of: September 2011**

### Acknowledgment

mailVU.com is a part of the A2Stream Inc. family of businesses. We are committed to protecting your  
privacy. This Privacy Policy provides our privacy practices in regards to the information we collect  
when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing http://mailVU.com or A2Stream's  
applications or widgets for social networks (including but not limited to Facebook), you acknowledge  
and fully understand this Privacy Policy, agree to be bound by the terms contained in this Policy, and  
freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy.

You further acknowledge and agree that you are at least 18 years old, or have the permission of a  
parent or guardian. If you are under 18 years old and don't have permission from a parent or guardian  
you do not have permission to use this site. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role  
in their children's online activities and interests.

### Public Areas

mailVU.com may make certain information such as forums and blogs available to the public. The user  
must remember that all information disclosed in public areas such as forum comments or feedback  
comments may be publicly accessible. We cannot control who reads your postings or what they  
do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution when deciding to disclose  
personal information. The user has both the capability, and the responsibility, to designate the  
recipients of their mail, and the ability to set a deletion time period.

### Collection of Personal Information.

For certain services you need a mailVU.com user account. When you register we request personal  
information which may include your name, address, phone number, email address, username,  
password, and other relevant information. We may record information about your usage of our site,  
such as number of uploaded files and frequency and size of data transfers.

A2Stream may collect non-personally identifying information provided by your browser as you use  
the service. Information collected may include the IP Address, the time and date of your request, and  
actions taken on the web site. Additional information may include browser type and version, Internet  
connection type, webcam availability. We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may  
collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience. We  
may also use standard Internet tools, such as web beacons, which collect information that tracks your  
use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements. Information collected  
by mailVU.com is used to operate the services, and to further develop and improve the service.

A2Stream may store your information in any country. By using the mailVU.com service you consent  
that A2Stream may store, process, and transfer your personal information to any country.

### Use of Personal Information

We may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our services and products. Only mailVU.com  
will send you these direct mailings, and only if you have not opted out. You may change your opt-out  
preference at any time.

Testimonials posted on our web site are only placed with the expressed permission of the individual or  
company who provided that testimonial.

We may use cookies, web beacons, and logging information to a) store information so you don't have  
to retype it, b) provide custom, personalized content and information, c) monitor the effectiveness  
of our marketing campaigns, d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and page  
views, and e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

We may allow advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our website. We  
do not provide any personal information to these companies. Cookies and/or web beacons may be  
placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of advertising campaigns  
or email communications. You should visit those service provider's web pages to review their privacy  
policies. We prohibit web beacons from being used by third parties to collect or access your personally  
identifiable information.

### Sharing Information with 3rd Parties

We will not rent or sell your personal information to any other company or individual without your  
consent, except as we are required by law, or if disclosure of information is necessary to protect  
A2Stream, the mailVU.com users, or the general public. We reserve the right to report to law  
enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

You may provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us regarding third parties. For instance  
when you share Private links with others you may provide and we collect the email addresses of the  
people with whom you want to share your video and resume. We will not sell or rent Personally  
Identifiable Information to others, nor disclose the information to others except to the extent necessary  
to fulfill your service request, to protect ourselves from liability, to respond to a court order or  
subpoena, or in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

A2Stream may retain service providers to assist us with marketing, communications, and customer  
service initiatives. These providers could include providers of customer support, email service  
providers, automated data providers, and shipping agents. Suppliers and service providers are required  
by contract to keep confidential the information received on behalf of A2Stream and may not use it for  
any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for A2Stream.

Non account holders may view your mail if you designated them as recipients.

We do not store your credit card or other payment information on our site. Payment for services are  
made through an online billing transaction partner.

We may share with third parties non-personal, aggregated information, such as demographic and  
profile data of the user community at large.

### Your Choice in Selecting Privacy Settings

Every account holder is provided with a Profile section in their account. It is the responsibility of each  
user to ensure the information is correct and current. Users are responsible for the accuracy of their  
account profile. You may update or correct these selections as any time by logging into your account  
and making the changes on the page. You may leave any optional information fields blank.

The user has the option to opt-out of mailVU.com notifications. This option does not apply to

communications primarily for the purpose of administering order completion, support, software  
warnings and updates, or other administrative and transactional notices as the primary purpose of these  
communications is not promotional in nature.

The user must specify the deletion time period of each multimedia mail. The files will be deleted from  
the A2Stream servers at the earlier of the user defined date/views, or the time frame associated with  
your account type.

### Access to and Accuracy of Your Information

The mailVU.com site is generally accessible 24x7 every day of the year unless down for system  
maintenance or an outage. To protect your privacy and security on Premium accounts, we will take  
reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring username and password, before granting  
access to the data. To view and modify your personal information you may edit the selections in the  
Preferences page of the web site.

### Keeping Your Personal information Secure

A2Stream takes seriously the trust you place in us. We will keep your private data secure consistent  
with current industry standards. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data  
accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, A2Stream utilizes appropriate physical,  
technical, and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

Personal information, once transmitted to us, will be stored on computers that only selected personnel  
and contractors have access to via password. These computer systems are located in controlled  
facilities which have limited access. Your mail messages are limited-access, where access is gained  
through an obscured URL system. This obscured URL makes it difficult if not impossible for a third  
party to guess the URL address of your content without an invitation from you including the relevant  
URL. However, unless the videos and content are password protected, your invitees may forward the  
URL link to other parties and a possibility exists that an unauthorized third party could discover your  
videos and/or content.

### Changes to This Policy

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When  
we do, we will also revise the Update date located at the beginning of this Policy. We encourage you  
to periodically review this Policy and become aware of modifications. If we make material changes in  
the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you for sending an email to  
the email address you most recently provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes  
on our website. Your continued use of the mailVU.com site constitutes your agreement to this Policy  
and any updates.

### Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, its implementation, failure to adhere to the  
statement, or our general practices, please contact us at:

A2Stream Inc.  
support@a2stream.com  
9935-D Rae Rd., #113  
Charlotte, NC 28277  
704-237-0102

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
